Guide to the Brooklyn periodical illustrations BCMS.0003
Brooklyn Collection
- Portraits
  - Malone, Sylvester (Rev.) (Box 4)
  - The Managers of the New York and Brooklyn Theatres. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1867-02-16 (Box 4)
  - Mairs, William H. (Box 4)
  - Mann, Edward C. (M.D.) (Box 4)
  - Meyer, Julius E. (Box 4)
  - Millard, Orvill A. (Box 4)
  - Miller, Benjamin C. (Box 4)
  - Miller, Francis (M.D.) (Box 4)
  - Miller, Samuel B. (Box 4)
  - Mitchell, Chauncey L. (M.D.) (Box 4)
  - Moody, Leonard. (Box 4)
  - Morris, Samuel D. (Box 4)
  - Morton, John. (Box 4)
  - Murphy, Henry C. (Box 4)
  - Murtha, W.H. (Hon.) (Box 4)
  - Norris, Thomas P. (M.D.) (Box 4)
  - O'Brien, Patrick F. (Box 4)
  - O'Donohue, Joseph J. (Box 4)
  - Olcott, Cornelius (M.D.) (Box 4)
  - Orr, Alexander Ector. (Box 4)
  - Ostrander, Ferd. W. (M.D.) (Box 4)
  - Peace, Harvey W. (Box 4)
  - Pearce, Henry O. (Box 4)
  - Pearsall, G. Frank. (Box 4)
  - Pearse, Hosea O. (Box 4)
  - Peck, Edgar C. (M.D.) (Box 4)
  - Peed, Charles N. (Box 4)
  - Perry, Andrew J. (Esq.) (Box 4)
  - Perry, Joseph A. (Box 4)
  - Perry, Timothy. (Box 4)
  - Peters, Bernard. (Box 4)
  - Pierrepont, Henry E. (Box 4)
  - Pierrepont, Hez. B. (Box 4)
  - Pinto, Francis E. (Box 4)
  - Polhemus, Henny D. (Box 4)
  - Pratt, Calvin E. (Hon.) (Box 4)
  - Preston, William Irvine. (Box 4)
  - Rapalye, Williamson. (Box 4)
  - Rapelye, Jacob. (Box 4)
  - Rappelyea, Jeremiah. (Box 4)
  - Reynolds, Charles H. (Box 4)
  - Richardson, Leonard. (Box 4)
  - Ridley, Edward. (Box 4)
  - Rivers, Charles H. (Box 4)
  - Robbins, Amos. (Box 4)
  - Robbins, Daniel C. (Box 4)
  - Robbins, Eli. (Box 4)
  - Robinson, Jeremiah P. (Box 4)
  - Robinson, William Erigena. (Box 4)
  - Rodwell, James. (Box 4)
  - Roebling, Emily (Mrs. Washington A. Roebling). Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1883-06-09 (Box 4)
  - Roehr, Henry Edward (Col.) (Box 4)
  - Rome, John. (Box 4)
  - Runcie, John T. (Box 4)
  - Rutan, Thomas. (Box 4)
  - Saxton, Daniel Y. (Box 4)
  - Schenck, James. (Box 4)
  - Scott, Rufus L. (Box 4)
  - Seitz, Michael. (Box 4)
  - Shearman, Thomas G. (Esq.) (Box 4)
  - Sheldon, Henry. (Box 4)
  - Silliman, Benjamin. (Box 4)
  - Sizer, Nelson. (Box 4)
  - Skinner, David Salmon. (Box 4)
  - Skinner, Salmon (M.D.) (Box 4)
  - Smith, Dennis E. (Box 4)
  - Smith, Edward. (Box 4)
  - Smith, Thomas C. (Box 4)
  - Smith, Thomas L. (Box 4)
  - Snedecker, Elbert. (Box 4)
  - Speir, Robert. (Box 4)
  - Speir, Samuel Fleet (M.D.) (Box 4)
  - Spicer Jr., Elihu. (Box 4)
  - Sprague, William E. (Box 4)
  - Stearns, John M. (Box 4)
  - Stegman, Lewis R. (Box 4)
  - Storer, Samuel. (Box 4)
  - Storrs, Charles. (Box 4)
  - Storrs, Richard S. (Rev. D.D.) (Box 4)
  - Stranahan, J.S.T. (Hon.) (Box 4)
  - Sumner, William O. (Box 4)
  - Suydam, Adrian M. (Box 4)
  - Talmage, Thomas Dewitt (Rev. D.D.) (Box 4)
  - Tanner, James. (Box 4)
  - Tate, Augustus C. (Box 4)
  - Taylor, James A. (Box 4)
  - Taylor, William. (Box 4)
  - Taylor, William R. (Box 4)
  - Terry, Edmund. (Box 4)
  - Thomas, W.M. (Box 4)
  - Thompson, George L. (Hon.) (Box 4)
  - Tracy, Benjamin F. (Hon.) (Box 4)
  - Trask, Alanson. (Box 4)
  - Turner, John S. (Box 4)
  - Tuttle, Ezra B. (Box 4)
  - Tuttle, Silvester. (Box 4)
  - Van Buren, Robert (C.E.) (Box 4)
  - Vanderveer, Charles. (Box 4)
  - Vanderveer, Stephen L. (Box 4)
  - Vining, Harrison S. (Box 4)
  - Voorhies, John A. (Box 4)
  - Wackerhagen, George (M.D.) (Box 4)
  - Wall, Charles. (Box 4)
  - Wall, Michael W. (Box 4)
  - Wall, William (Hon.) (Box 4)
  - Wallace, James P. (Box 4)
  - Waring, William H. (Hon.) (Box 4)
  - Weaver, James. (Box 4)
  - Weidmann, Paul. (Box 4)
  - Wells, Lindsay James. (Box 4)
  - West, Benjamin W. (Box 4)
  - Williams, John. (Box 4)
  - Wischmann, Herman. (Box 4)
  - Woodruff, Albert. (Box 4)
  - Woodruff, Franklin. (Box 4)
- Race Relations
  - A Brooklyn Episode. Puck, 1892 (Box 5)
- Racetracks
  - The Brooklyn Suburban Handicap. Collier's Weekly, 1896 July 2 (Box 5)
  - The Coney Island Cup Race. Drawn by Edwin Forbes. Harper's Weekly, 1881-07-09 (Box 5)
  - Coney Island Jockey Club – The Great Match-Race between Tenny and Salvator for a Purse of Fifteen Thousand Dollars. The Horses Coming Down the Home Stretch. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1890-07-05 (Box 5)
  - The Cresceus-Abbot Trotting Race, Brighton Beach, Aug. 15. The Commercial Advertiser, 1901-08-24 (Box 5)
  - Das Pferderennen auf der Rennebahn von Sheepshead Bay am 10 Juni 1886—Troubadour, Siege vom vierten Rennen [The horse race on the racetrack of Sheepshead Bay on June 10 1886-Troubadour, victories of the fourth race]. Frank Leslie's Illustrierte Zeitung, 1886-06-19 (Box 5)
  - Das Suburban Handicap des Coney Island Jockey Club [The Suburban Handicap of the Coney Island Jockey Club]. Frank Leslie's Illustrierte Zeitung, 1895 (Box 5)
  - The Fall Racing Season – Characteristic Scenes on the Course of the Coney Island Jockey Club. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1888-09-15 (Box 5)
  - The "Futurity," Run at the Meeting of the Coney Island Jockey Club at Sheepshead Bay, August 27. Harper's Weekly [?], undated. (Box 5)
  - The "Futurity" at Sheepshead Bay, August 31. Harper's Weekly, 1901 (Box 5)
  - The Futurity at Sheepshead Bay Track, Aug. 31. The Commercial Advertiser, 1901-09-07 (Box 5)
  - James R. Keene's "Superman" winning the Brooklyn Handicap. Harper's Weekly, 1907 (Box 5)
  - July 4th Special Programme of Seven Races by the Coney Island Jockey Club [race announcement]. Harper's Weekly, 1894 (Box 5)
  - Opening Day at the Brooklyn Jockey Club, May 25. The Commercial Advertiser, 1901-06-01 (Box 5)
  - Opening of the Racing Season of the Brooklyn Jockey Club, May 15th – The Brooklyn Handicap: Scene at the Finish. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1889-05-25 (Box 5)
  - Prize-Winners in the New York Speedway Parade., Undated. (Box 5)
  - The Race between Cresceus and the Abbot at Brighton Beach. Harper's Weekly, 1895 (Box 5)
  - Racing at Brighton Beach, Coney Island. Drawn by P. Frenzeny. Harper's Weekly, 1882-09-30 (Box 5)
  - The Racing Season of 1893: Scenes and Incidents at Sheepshead Bay, Morris Park, and Coney Island. Harper's Weekly, 1893-07-27 (Box 5)
  - Scenes at the Sheepshead Bay Racing Course. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Weekly, 1889-09-07 (Box 5)
  - Sketches at the Suburban at Coney Island. Frank Leslie's Weekly, 1892-06-23 (Box 5)
  - A Snap-Shot of the Crowd in Front of the Grand-Stand at the Brooklyn Handicap, Run at Gravesend, May 26. Harper's Weekly [?], 1904 (Box 5)
  - A Steeple-Chase on the Course at Sheepshead Bay – Taking "The Water Jump." Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1883-06-30 (Box 5)
  - Steeple-Chasing at the Metropolitan Race-Tracks—The "Grand National." Harper's Weekly. (Box 5)
  - The Suburban Finish. Harper's Weekly, 1891-06-27 (Box 5)
  - The Summer Meeting of the Coney Island Jockey Club. At Sheepshead Bay – Rejoicing of the Stable Followers over the Success of the Favorite. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1881-07-09 (Box 5)
  - Trot on the Fashion Racecourse, L.I., May 30. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1865-06-24 (Box 5)
  - The Trotting Season at Prospect Park Fair Grounds, L.I. – Race between "Fullerton" and "Goldsmith Maid," Monday, June 8th. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1874-06-27 (Box 5)
  - Weighing In. Opening of the Racing Season: First Day of the Spring Meeting of the Brooklyn Jockey Club. The Illustrated American, 1894-06-02 (Box 5)
- Railroads
  - The Brooklyn, Bath and Coney Island Railroad, 1874 [?] (Box 5)
  - The Eastern Power Station of the Brooklyn City Railroad Company. Scientific American, 1894 September 8 (Box 5)
  - Opening of the Brooklyn Elevated Railway, May 13. Harper's Weekly, 1885 May 23 (Box 5)
- Real Estate
  - $10 Secures a $480 Lot in Greater New York. Collier's Weekly, 1902 March 15 (Box 5)
  - If You Could Make $5,000 by Paying $6 a Month--$510. in All – Would You do It? Leslie's Weekly, 1903 February 19 (Box 5)
  - Subway Lots Bring Millions, 1911 November 2 [?] (Box 5)
- Revivals
  - The Distressing Failure of the Brooklyn Revival Business. Puck, 1881 March 30 (Box 5)
  - The Fulton Street Prayer-Meeting. Harper's Weekly, 1871-09-30 (Box 5)
  - Messrs. Moody and Sankey, the Revivalists Conducting, Sunday, Oct. 24th, the First of a Series of Meetings at the Rink, on Clermont Avenue. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1875-11-13 (Box 5)
  - Our Spiritual Guardians. Puck, undated. (Box 5)
  - Praise and Exhortation Service of the Salvation Army on the Steps of the City Hall, Brooklyn. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1882-08-19 (Box 5)
  - The Revivalists in Brooklyn – The Crowd Before the Rink in Clermont Avenue. Harper's Weekly, 1875-11-13 (Box 5)
  - The Rival Revivals in Brooklyn. Puck, undated. (Box 5)
  - Tabernacle Free Baths! Prof. Talmage, Bathing Master [German language]. Puck, 1880 (Box 5)
- Sanitary Fair
  - Brooklyn Fair in Aid of the Sanitary Commission [2 copies]. Harper's Weekly, 1864 March 5 (Box 8)
  - Brooklyn Sanitary Fair, 1864. Interior View of the Academy of Music as Seen from the Dress Circle. Lithograph of A.Brown & Co. 47 Nassau St. N.Y., Undated. (Box 8)
  - Brooklyn Sanitary Fair, 1864. Lithograph of A.Brown & Co. 47 Nassau St. N.Y., Undated. (Box 8)
  - Brooklyn Sanitary Fair, 1864. New England Kitchen. Lithograph of A.Brown & Co. 47 Nassau St. N.Y., Undated. (Box 8)
  - Brooklyn Sanitary Fair, 1864. View of the Academy of Music. Lithograph of A.Brown & Co. 47 Nassau St. N.Y., Undated. (Box 8)
  - Brooklyn Sanitary Fair, 1864, View of the Academy of Music as Seen from the Stage. Lithograph of A.Brown & Co. 47 Nassau St. N.Y.], Undated. (Box 8)
  - The New England Kitchen Spinners at the Brooklyn Sanitary Fair. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1864-03-12 (Box 8)
  - The Opening of the Metropolitan Sanitary Fair – Bird's-Eye View of Fourteenth Street. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1864-04-16 (Box 8)
  - The Sanitary Fair at Brooklyn - The Academy of Music, Montague Street, with the Bridge Across to the New England Kitchens Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1864, 1864-03-05 (Box 8)
  - The Sanitary Fair at Brooklyn – The New England Kitchen – From a sketch by our special artist. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1864-03-12 (Box 8)
  - "Anything for me, if you please?" -- Post Office of the Brooklyn Fair in Aid of the Sanitary Comission. Harper's Weekly, 1864-03-05 (Box 8)
- Schools
  - The Highest Point of Brooklyn Morality Reached at Last: Lowell, Whittier, and Holmes. – If Longfellow Is Found Improper, What Hope Is There for Us? Puck, undated (Box 5)
  - The Pratt Industrial Institute, Brooklyn, New York. Harper's Weekly, 1887-11-19 (Box 5)
  - The Pratt Institute. Brooklyn, New York—the Pupils at Work. Harper's Weekly, 1891-03-21 (Box 5)
  - Pratt Institute for Industrial Education, Brooklyn, N.Y. – The Largest Institution of the Kind in the World. Scientific American, 1888-10-06 (Box 5)
  - Public School No. 136; Public School No. 124; Public School No 127; Public School No. 108 [see ARCHITECTURE – verso of Ansonia Clock Company]. King's Views of Brooklyn, 1904 (Box 5)
- Social Welfare
  - An American Eviction for Non-Payment of Rent. A Scene in South Brooklyn. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1888 January 28 (Box 5)
  - The Club-Rooms of "The Christian Union for Chinese Work" in Brooklyn—Ladies Teaching Pupils the Alphabet. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1883-10-06 (Box 5)
  - An Eviction Scene at "Darby's Patch" in Brooklyn—Attempted Expulsion of an Army of Squatters. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1883-12-08 (Box 5)
  - The Fresh Air Charities of New York. Harper's Weekly, 1894 (Box 5)
  - The Graham Institution for Aged Females, Brooklyn. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1870-12-24 (Box 5)
  - Home for Destitute Children, Butler Street, Brooklyn. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1880-02-21 (Box 5)
  - A Longshoremen's Retreat, Brooklyn., Undated. (Box 5)
  - The Poor of New York City—A Hot Night on the East River Front: An Officer on Watch. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1889-07-13 (Box 5)
  - "Waiting" – A scene in the Old Ladies' Home, Brooklyn. Harper's Weekly, 1867-06-13 (Box 5)
- Sports
  - Aquatic sports – The Attempt of Miss Agnes Beckwith to Swim from Sandy Hook to Coney Island, June 30th. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1883 July 14 (Box 5)
  - The Archery Tournament, Prospect Park, Brooklyn. Harper's Weekly, 1881-07-23 (Box 5)
  - The "Atlantic" Baseball Club of Brooklyn and the "Athletic" of Philadelphia. Harper's Weekly, 1866-11-03 (Box 5)
  - "Champion Nine" of the Atlantic Base-Ball Club of Brooklyn, L.I. Harper's Weekly, 1865-11-25 (Box 5)
  - Cricket in America – Snap-Shots of Scenes in Public Matches at Prospect Park, Brooklyn. Harper's Weekly, undated. (Box 5)
  - Eleventh Annual and First Union Regatta of the Brooklyn Yacht Club, Tuesday June 25 [see Churches: The Ceremony of Laying the Corner Stone of the Roman Catholic Cathedral of the Immaculate Conception—two illustrations on one page]. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1868-07-11 (Box 5)
  - Extraordinary Skating – Mr. Axel Paulsen at the Washington Park Rink, Brooklyn. Harper's Weekly, 1884-02-16 (Box 5)
  - Fancy Skating at the Union Pond, Williamsburg, L.I.—Mr. Engler and Miss Bedell Executing the Backward Roll. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1867-02-09 (Box 5)
  - Game of baseball in the Thirteenth Regiment Armory, Brooklyn, between members of the regiment – "Striker Out." Harper's Weekly, 1890-03-08 (Box 5)
  - Grand Match between the Athletic Base Ball Club of Philadelphia, and the Resolute Club of Brooklyn, NY, Thursday June 15th, at the Union Ground, Brooklyn. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1865-07-01 (Box 5)
  - An Hour in a Hand-Ball Court in Brooklyn. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1888-12-29 (Box 5)
  - Madame Anderson's Plucky Walk. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1879-02-01 (Box 5)
  - New Ice Planer and Snow Clearer at Work at Union Pond, Brooklyn E.D., New York. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1868-08-22 (Box 5)
  - New Quarters and Playground of the Westchester Polo Club, in Prospect Park, Brooklyn – Opening Match of the Season, June 11th. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper (Box 5)
  - New York – Tournament of the Association for the Protection of Game and Fish, at Coney Island. The Pigeon-Shooting – from sketches by a staff artist. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1881-07-09 (Box 5)
  - Roller-skating at the Brooklyn Rink – Juvenile Skaters Performing "The Chase of the Butterfly." Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1877-05-12 (Box 5)
  - Skating Carnival in Brooklyn, February 10, 1862. Harper's Weekly, 1862-02-22 (Box 5)
  - Some Recent Sporting Events—The Intercollegiate Sports and the Brooklyn Handicap. Collier's Weekly, 1897-06-10 (Box 5)
  - The Sportsmen's Tournament at Coney Island - Methods of Trapping and Transporting the Pigeons for use in the Contests. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1881-07-02 (Box 5)
  - Winter in New York: Sleighing on the New "Ocean Parkway," Brooklyn. The Pictoral World, 1877-03-10 (Box 5)
  - Winter Quarters of Well-Known Yachts at Tebo's Yard, Brooklyn. Frank Leslie's Weekly, 1892-03-24 (Box 5)
  - Yacht Rendezvous, Gowanus Bay, Brooklyn – Preparing for the Yachting Season. Harper's Weekly, 1877-06-09 (Box 5)
- Strikes
  - The Great Street-Railway Strike in New York and Brooklyn. The strikers and their friends building barricades on Carmine Street, New York City; The mounted police of Brooklyn escorting a gang of "scabs" and a provision-wagon to the Ninth Avenue and Nineteenth Street stables. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1889 February 9 (Box 6)
  - The Street-Car Strike in Brooklyn. Harper's Weekly, undated. (Box 6)
  - The Streetcar Strike in Brooklyn—Starting the First Car. Harper's Weekly, 1889-02-09 (Box 6)
  - The Strike in Brooklyn. Detachment of the Forty-Seventh Regiment Marching to Fifteenth Street; Halsey Street and Broadway – The Shooting of Ahrens; Trolley-Car Used as an Ambulance [2 copies]., Undated. (Box 6)
  - The Strike in Brooklyn – Firing at the Mob [2 copies]. Harper's Weekly, undated. (Box 6)
  - The Strike in Brooklyn – First Battery, Stationed at East New York; Seventh Regiment Deploying Skirmishers at Ridgewood Stables – Taking out the First Car, January 22nd. Harper's Weekly, undated. (Box 6)
  - The Strike in Brooklyn – "Keep the Windows Down!" [2 copies]. Harper's Weekly, undated. (Box 6)
  - The Strike in Brooklyn – [Recto: Troop A Awaiting Orders; Troop A Preparing Dinner; Cooking Meals; Troop A Going to Escort the Linemen's Wagon; Thirteenth Regiment Pickets Trying to Keep Warm. Verso: Major William H. Kipp; Major G.G. Cochran; Captain Charles F. Roe; "The Triangle," a Saloon Frequented by the Strikers, at Broadway and Halsey Street [2 copies]. Harper's Weekly, undated. (Box 6)
- Transportation
  - An Exciting Daily Scene in New York. The Struggle of the Returning Crowd of Brooklyn Visitors. Leslie's Weekly, 1899 April 6 (Box 6)
  - A Few Facts Concerning the Crowded Cars of the Brooklyn Anti-Fat Surface Railroad Company. Puck, 1884 (Box 6)
  - Mechanism for Operating the Cars of the Brooklyn Bridge. Scientific American, 1883-10-13 (Box 6)
  - Method of Working the Car-Cable of the East River Bridge., Undated. (Box 6)
  - The Only Way For Weyler to Keep the Cuban Insurgents from Crossing his "Trocha." He Will Have to Get Some Brooklyn Trolley Cars and Motor Men, and Keep Them Running Up and Down the Line at Full Speed., Undated. (Box 6)
  - The Proposed East River Tunnel. Scientific American, 1899-07-01 (Box 6)
  - Rapid Transit Subway at the Battery and East River Tunnel, New York. Scientific American, 1902-12-20 (Box 6)
  - Street Postal Car System - Comparted Car. Scientific American, 1896-02-29 (Box 6)
  - Train Telephony. Telephoning from Moving Cars. Scientific American, 1896-04-04 (Box 6)
- Utilities
  - The Brooklyn Waterworks Celebration. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1859 May 14 (Box 6)
  - Excavating and Pipe Laying Apparatus in Use on the Brooklyn Aqueduct. Scientific American, 1891-01-03 (Box 6)
  - Fire-Works at Brooklyn City Hall, on the Inauguration of the Water-Works. Harper's Weekly, 1859-05-14 (Box 6)
  - A Great Sewer Built by an Improved Method of Tunneling, in Brooklyn, N.Y. Scientific American, 1886-01 (Box 6)
  - The Great Storm Sewer in Brooklyn, New York. Scientific American, 1892-01-30 (Box 6)
  - An Impure Source of Brooklyn Water – Horsebrook and the Hempstead Reservoir. Harper's Weekly, undated. (Box 6)
  - Knowles' Improved Compound Condensing Pumping Engines at the Brooklyn Water Works. Scientific American, 1886-04-10 (Box 6)
  - Mount Prospect Laboratory. Scientific American Supplement, 1900-06-30 (Box 6)
  - The New High Service Water Tower, Brooklyn, N.Y., Prospect Park Plaza. Scientific American, 1892-09-03 (Box 6)
  - The Recent Serious Aqueduct Disaster in Brooklyn, which Threatened a Water Famine in the City. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Weekly, 1891-12-12 (Box 6)
  - Triumphal Arch Erected in the Eastern District of the City of Brooklyn, on the Occasion of the Waterworks Celebration. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1859-05-14 (Box 6)
- Veterans
  - The Battle-Scarred and Limbless Veterans of the Brooklyn Regiments, Long Island, Being Conveyed in Carriages in the Procession to Fort Greene, to Receive their Medals, Thursday Oct.25. [also a German language version]. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1866 November 10 (Box 6)
  - Issuing Christmas Dinners to the Veterans in Brooklyn. Harper's Weekly, undated. (Box 6)
  - Patriotic Brooklyn Children [children presenting money collected for the Labor Bureau and Emergency Fund of the Grand Army of the Republic]. Munsey's Illustrated Weekly, 1884-10-18 (Box 6)
  - Presentation of Medals by the Mayor and Corporation of Brooklyn, at Fort Greene, to the Veterans of the Brooklyn Regiments Engaged in the Late War, Thursday, Oct. 25th. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1866-11-10 (Box 6)
  - Presentation of Medals in Brooklyn. Medals Presented to the Veterans of Brooklyn. Harper's Weekly, undated. (Box 6)
  - Presentation of Medals to the Veterans of Brooklyn. Harper's Weekly, 1866-11-10 (Box 6)
  - Reception of the Ninetieth New York Veteran Volunteers in Brooklyn. Harper's Weekly, 1866-03-03 (Box 6)
  - Veterans of Brooklyn Regiment, near Fort Greene. [German language]. Frank Leslie's Illustrierte Zeitung, 1866-11-17 (Box 6)
  - Veterans "Fighting their Battles over Again." An Evening Scene at a Grand Army Post Headquarters in Brooklyn. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1888-12-08 (Box 6)
- Views
  - The Age of Sky-Scrapers—Tall Buildings in the Business District of New York City. Harper's Weekly (Box 6)
  - The Battle Pass. Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884 (Box 6)
  - Bedford Corners. Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884 (Box 6)
  - City of New York from Brooklyn Heights. New York, D.Appleton & Co., 1872 (Box 6)
  - The Eastern District Water Front. King's Views of Brooklyn, 1904 (Box 6)
  - Evacuation-Day – The Great Marine Parade, As Viewed from the Brooklyn Tower of the Bridge. Drawn by Charles Graham. Harper's Weekly, 1883-12-08 (Box 6)
  - Fire-Works at New York on the Evening of the Fourth of July, as Seen from Brooklyn Heights. Harper's Weekly, 1859-07-16 (Box 6)
  - Fulton Street, from the Ferry, Brooklyn N.Y., Undated. (Box 6)
  - Guy's Brooklyn Snow Scene. Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884 (Box 6)
  - Harlem River at Washington Bridge. The Sun, 1914-12-13 (Box 6)
  - Lamport & Holt Line, Brazil and River Plate Steamships, Furman Street, base of Columbia Heights. King's Views of Brooklyn, 1904 (Box 6)
  - Long Island Sound. Painted by Jas. A Suyden and engraved by S.V. Hunt., Undated. (Box 6)
  - Looking Northwest from the Temple Bar Building, Court and Joralemon Sts. King's Views of Brooklyn, 1904 (Box 6)
  - Lower Part of the City of New York, from the Bay., Undated. (Box 6)
  - New York and Brooklyn from Williamsburg., Undated. (Box 6)
  - New York Bay During the Cold Spell. Harper's Weekly, undated. (Box 6)
  - The New York of the Future – An Artist's Prophetic Vision of Manhattan and Governor's Islands, And The Brooklyn and Jersey Shores. Leslie's Weekly, 1906 (Box 6)
  - Returning from John I's (Snedicker). Ballou's Pictorial, 1855 (Box 6)
  - St. Marks Place, near Brooklyn Avenue. Harper's New Monthly Magazine, 1893 (Box 6)
  - Unwholesome Environs of Brooklyn., 1894 (Box 6)
  - View from Fort Hamilton, New York Harbor – the Sunset Gun. Harper's Weekly, 1879-05-10 (Box 6)
  - View from Gowanus Heights, Brooklyn. Print published by Geo. Virtue., 1839 (Box 6)
  - View from Ground Appropriated for the Clinton Monument (Greenwood Cemetery)., Undated. (Box 6)
  - View in Remsen Street. Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884 (Box 6)
  - View of Brooklyn. Drawn & Lith by G. Hayward, 171 Pearl St., NY., 1840 (Box 6)
  - View of Brooklyn from the Foot of Wall Street; U.S. Navy Yard; Packer Institute. Ballou's Pictorial Drawing Room Companion, 1857 (Box 6)
  - View of the Bay of New York from the Battery. Designed and engraved for the New Mirror by W.J. Bennett., Undated. (Box 6)
  - View of the City and Harbor of New York, from the Heights at Brooklyn, on Long Island., Undated. (Box 6)
  - View of the City of Brooklyn, NY, from the Granite Quay. Gleason's Pictorial Drawing Room Companion, 1851-08-09 (Box 6)
  - View of the Fulton Ferry Buildings, Brooklyn, Long Island. Ballou's Pictorial Drawing Room Companion, 1855 (Box 6)
  - Wallabout Market. King's Views of Brooklyn, 1904 (Box 6)
  - The World's Greatest Seaport and its 771-Mile Waterfront., Undated. (Box 6)
- Wars: Revolutionary War
  - The Battle of Long Island: Colonel Henry "Light-Horse" Lee. The National Guard Heritage, undated (Box 6)